P
N.
I never say hello
love
this one.
M
is
disaster and joy
h.
during those first months
they had sex
they got to know each other in many ways,
and realized that she would behave differently towards others
but especially towards a man,
a young man.
He seems to be the most humble
so as not to burden
his bride.
so that he sees her that way
if you're too busy in that first moment together,
that's not good
because you don't know your partner.
And hiding something
and then it comes later
is also bad.
if it's a boy
he likes something
-- he tells his bride that now there are
-- games.
-- but playing is also
-- good for couples
married
so while you're at it, how about playing
how about
so that's the answer.
We welcome our followers on Murinzi TV and we are now in a family program
Today we are with our parents who have come for advice
and we are going to discuss issues related to
and social life and good relationships at home
which are things that can build a family,
and family in need at this time
we hope you will benefit a lot.
We are with the father Pastor Kagoyera Simeon,
who is with our mother, the lady, let's hurry up.
you guys
the audience
This conversation.
No
on TV
I am old.
in the name of Jesus Christ
may God's peace be with you,
My name is Simeon Kagwera.
As Lotel said.
I am a pastor.
At the Seventh-day Adventist Church in Abad City.
And I was retired.
Yes
and my mother continues
I greet you in the name of Jesus,
here we are in the family
of Pastor Kagera Simeon.
We thank God very much
for the family we have
and my name is Prisca Mukantagara
and I am the wife of Pastor Kagorera Simeon
we have brought you the last time.